gono.ph 2016-01-12

# 

## ParkLogic Privacy Policy

ParkLogic has developed this Privacy Statement to inform you about how we deal with privacy issues in relation to our website and other ParkLogic services.  
**  
Overview  
** The ParkLogic Team is committed to ensuring ParkLogic's services are secure and private service. We fully comply with the best practice standards recommended by the Internet Industry Association of Australia and Federal privacy laws. When you visit the ParkLogic website, we can record certain information in relation to your visit such as:  
\- your IP or proxy server IP;   
\- basic domain information;   
\- your Internet service provider is sometimes captured depending upon the configuration of your ISP connection;   
\- the date and time of your visit to the website;   
\- the length of your session;   
\- the pages which you have accessed;   
\- the number of times you access our site within any month;   
\- the size of files you look at;   
\- the website which referred you to our website;   
\- the type and version of the browser you are using;   
\- the operating system which your computer uses.   
This information is only used for statistical and website development purposes.Various pages in the ParkLogic site invite you to email us your name and contact details, for example to sign up to use the ParkLogic services. ParkLogic will not otherwise collect information from you through this web site unless you knowingly provide it to us. This web site only uses session cookies, which are used only during a browsing session, and expire when you quit your browser. Upon closing your browser the session cookie set by this web site is destroyed and no personal information is maintained which might identify you should you visit our web site at a later date.  
**  
Use Of Information  
ParkLogic will only use the information it collects through this website for the following purposes:** \- Forwarding important information relating to ParkLogic activities and other requested information;   
\- We may contact you in response to your feedback or query to discuss our services;   
\- Monitoring web site performance;   
\- Improving our website and services to you;   
\- Internal administration; and   
\- Other purposes that are in accordance with your instructions.  ParkLogic will not give, sell, trade or otherwise disclose any personal information about you to a third party unless: \- You have provided us with your consent; or   
\- We are required to do so by law.  **Access and Correction  
** You can ask us for access to your personal information or you can ask us to correct or update your personal information.  
**  
Opt-In and Opt-Out  
** To protect you from unwanted email communications, ParkLogic adopts both an opt-in as well as opt-out facility for marketing communication. You are invited to opt in when you apply for services, through our web site, as well as through other communications with us. Other than in the course of our regular communication with customers and others with whom we deal, unless you initially opt-in, you will not be emailed by us unsolicited. If you have opted in, and later decide you would like to either receive, or no longer wish to receive communications from us, please advise us by sending an email to [**privacy@ParkLogic.com**](mailto:privacy@ParkLogic.com%20?subject=Privacy%20Policy) **Links to Other Sites  
**This site contains links to other sites. ParkLogic is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked sites.  
**  
Personal** **Data  
**ParkLogic may have a subscriber system designed to add value to a user's Internet experience. To experience all the benefits of the subscriber system, a user is required to register and submit their details and preferences. Information is also collected based on a user's surfing habits. Individual identifiable information will never be disclosed, revealed, sold, shared or passed on to any third party. Details are recorded so that a user can personalise their settings and so that they can experience the benefits of the subscriber system. The only exception, is where we are required by law to disclose information. All stored information is kept in a secure environment.   
**  
Subscriber Questionnaires  
**The ParkLogic Team will collect information that is volunteered by users via questionnaires. This information is only used to improve a user's Internet experience. These surveys are strictly confidential.   
**  
Aggregated Data  
**From time to time, ParkLogic may provide aggregated statistical information or non identifiable data to reputable third parties. This is not personally identifiable information and assists ParkLogic to provide you with a better service.   
**  
Cookies  
** A cookie is a message given to your web browser by a web server, which is stored for later use, so when a user visits that website your browser recognises their preferences. The use of cookies can enhance a user's surfing experience so that only relevant information is delivered to them based on their preferences.   
**  
Children  
**Children that are under the age of 18 must have consent of their legal guardians to become a user of ParkLogic services.  
**  
Security  
**This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorised access to information under our control. However if you send us information from this site, it will not be encrypted unless we expressly tell you it is.  
**  
Further Information  
**For further information about ParkLogic's privacy policy, please contact us by our website **.**[ ****](mailto:privacy@ParkLogic.com%20?subject=Privacy%20Policy)
